Guide to the Daniel Nilva Negatives PHOTOS 067
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series II: Labor Organizations.
  - Subseries II:D: American Labor Education Service.
    - Eleanor Roosevelt, American Labor Education Service; E.R. Addressing Lucilee Conn, Chairman of Board, Hotel Shelbourne, Nov 14, 1955 (Box 2, Item 947)
  - Subseries II:E: Congress of Industrial Organizations (CIO).
    - [Meeting in an auditorium or hotel ballroom, mainly speakers shown. Banners include legend, "CIO" and slogans "Organize the Unorganized White Collar Worker" "Hail the work of the CIO."], [1930s?] (Box 1, Item 586)
    - Furniture Salesmen, CIO Local 853, [1950s?] (Box 2, Item 892)
    - CIO Steel Hearings, [1950s?] (Box 2, Item 893)
    - CIO Convention, 1951 (Box 1, Item 719)
    - [CIO Convention, Hotel Commodore, New York City. Includes Michael Quill and Philip Murray.], Nov 1, 1951 (Box 2, Item 950)
    - CIO Convention, NYC, Nov 5, 1951-Nov 11, 1951 (Box 2, Item 889)
  - Subseries II:F: Harlem Labor Center.
    - [Harlem Labor Center meeting], [1950s?] (Box 2, Item 894)
    - [Meeting; Includes door labeled "Painters DC 9." Mostly African-American audience. Harlem Labor Center?], [1950s?] (Box 2, Item 895)
  - Subseries II:G: Histadrut.
    - Histadrut Luncheon, Hotel Astor, [1950s?] (Box 2, Item 912)
    - Histadrut Meeting, Hotel Astor, Dec 6, 1956 (Box 2, Item 896)
    - Histadrut, City Hall, Apr 4, 1957 (Box 2, Item 897)
    - Histadrut Luncheon for Moshe Bartal; Histadrut Representative to U.S.; Kruzo [Pincus Caruso], Paole Zion; J. Schlossberg; Sarah Surchin, Pioneer Women; Cecil Human, Isr. Con.; Moshe Bartal, Histadrut; Dr. Begun, Chairman; J. Breslan; I. Nagler; Eddie Euro; I. H. Goldberg, Hatters, May 10, 1957 (Box 2, Item 898)
    - Histadrut Dinner, Sheraton Astor, Sep 18, 1957 (Box 2, Item 900)
    - Histadrut, Phil Murray Luncheon, Commodore, Sep 24, 1957 (Box 2, Item 901)
    - Histadrut, J. Avidor [sp?], Israeli Ambassador to USSR, and Wife, Oct 10, 1957 (Box 2, Item 902)
    - Histadrut Conference, Commodore Hotel, Oct 27, 1957 (Box 2, Item 903)
    - Histadrut, Israeli Entertainers, Josefa Schocken, Shimon Finkel, Nov 19, 1957 (Box 2, Item 904)
    - Histadrut, Bessarabian [?] Committee, Hist. Hqtrs., Jan 2, 1958 (Box 2, Item 905)
    - Histadrut, [Annual] Service Luncheon, Park Plaza, Jan 6, 1958 (Box 2, Item 906)
    - Histadrut, Picker Equipment, Jan 10, 1958 (Box 2, Item 907)
    - Histadrut, Luncheon, Astor Hotel, Jan 16, 1958 (Box 2, Item 908)
    - Histadrut, Branch 400, Feb 1, 1958 (Box 2, Item 909)
    - Histadrut, District 65 Contribution, Oct 28, 1958 (Box 2, Item 910)
    - Histadrut, Books for Israel, Marty Cohn Donor, Dec 2, 1958 (Box 2, Item 911)
    - Histadrut, Check from Local 10, May 16, 1975 (Box 2, Item 899)
  - Subseries II:H: International Confederation of Free Trade Unions.
    - Free Trade Union Committee, ICFTU Luncheon: Francis, Edward, Tachin, Merison, Lovestone, Zimmerman; J. McLarin, Sleeping Car Porters; Noah Walters, Workmans Comp.; Maida Springer, Local 22 Laundry Workers; Ed Welsh, Rubber Workers; Louis Nelson, Local 155; Charles Zimmerman, Local 22; Gilbert and Jonas (Information Associates), [1960s?] (Box 2, Item 913)
  - Subseries II:I: International Workers Front Against War.
    - International Workers Front against War Convention, Oct 1, 1939 (Box 4, Item 78)
    - [International Workers Front against War (possibly affiliated with Communist Party Opposition), Meeting at Marxist Center. Diego Rivera murals are visible on the walls in the background.], ca.1939 (Box 2, Item 914)
  - Subseries II:J: Jewish Labor Committee (JLC).
    - Jewish Labor Council [Jewish Labor Committee?] Luncheon, Astor, Feb 12, 1949 (Box 1, Item 68)
    - Jewish Labor Committee: [Meeting or conference (possibly on the topic of discrimination in housing and education) held at a resort (probably the ILGWU's Unity House)., [1950s?] (Box 1, Item 720)
    - JLC Mural Presented to Workmen's Circle, [1950s?] (Box 2, Item 926)
    - Ceil Chapman, JLC, 530 7th Ave [Group photograph of workers in a shop and a meeting in an office. Ceil Chapman was a women's clothing designer. Perhaps this was her workshop and perhaps she is pictured in the meeting in the office.], Apr 27, 1950 (Box 2, Item 915)
    - Jewish Labor Committee, Mayor Wagner Swearing in, Charles Zimmerman, City Hall, Jan 19, 1955 (Box 2, Item 916)
    - JLC, [Photograph of a painting of B. Charney Vladeck speaking], Oct 27, 1955 (Box 2, Item 917)
    - Rand School [Conference called by the National Trade Union Committee for Racial Justice on the problems of African-American workers; at the Rand School, 7 East 15th Street, New York City], Nov 11, 1955 (Box 3, Item 1072)
    - Jewish Labor Committee, AFL-CIO Convention: Averell Harriman and Charles Zimmerman. [Also, Zimmerman with Adlai Stevenson; Gov. G. Menner Williams. In all four shots the men are posed in front of a sign that reads: "United House of Labor."], Dec 6, 1955 (Box 2, Item 918)
    - Jewish Labor Committee, Weekend Conference [National Trade Union Conference on Civil Rights], Belmont Plaza, May 4, 1956-May 6, 1956 (Box 2, Item 919)
    - Jewish Labor Committee: Hungarian Protest Meeting [Madison Square Garden], Averell Harriman [In shot #9, additional caption reads, "Pat and Schnitzler." "Pat" probably refers to JLC's Jacob Pat.], Nov 8, 1956 (Box 2, Item 920)
    - Jewish Labor Committee Emergency Conference, Belmont Plaza, Nov 30, 1956 (Box 2, Item 921)
    - Jewish Labor Committee [at?] (Housing Meeting), [AFSCME, Local 1707], Jun 23, 1958 (Box 2, Item 922)
    - Jewish Labor Committee, William Green Plaque, Feb 5, 1959 (Box 2, Item 923)
    - JLC, [Dedication of William Green Human Relations Library], Apr 20, 1959 (Box 2, Item 924)
    - Jewish Labor Committee, Mayor's Office, Apr 17, 1961 (Box 2, Item 925)
  - Subseries II:K: League for Industrial Democracy.
    - Student League for Industrial Democracy; [Meeting or lecture in auditorium; group portrait shot at a branch of the Workmen's Circle.], Dec 27, 1946 (Box 1, Item 67)
    - Luncheon Awards to Luis Munoz Marin, of Puerto Rico, Apr 13, 1957 (Box 2, Item 929)
  - Subseries II:L: New York City Central Labor Council.
    - Central Trades Council Rump Meeting for Judge Ferdinand Pecora, McAlpin [Hotel], [Oct 27, 1950?] (Box 1, Item 651)
  - Subseries II:M: Women's Trade Union League.
    - WTUL [Women's Trade Union League], Scholarships, Jun 11, 1957 (Box 2, Item 931)
- Series III: Political Parties and Organizations.
  - Subseries III:A: American Labor Party.
    - La Guardia [Madison Square Garden] [Signs/banners include slogans: American Labor Party/Re-elect La Guardia], [1938?] (Box 1, Item 555)
    - American Labor Party (Top Officials): [Alex] Rose, Jacob Potofsky, Luigi Antonini, Louis Hollander, Andrew Armstrong, C. Strebel, 1936 (Box 4, Item 236)
    - American Labor Party, Madison Square Garden Meeting, 1936 (Box 4, Item 89)
    - American Labor Party, Roosevelt, Wallace and Mead, [1940s?] (Box 1, Item 69)
  - Subseries III:B: British Labour Party.
    - British Labour Party, Herbert Morrison, [1960s?] (Box 1, Item 725)
  - Subseries III:C: Independent Communist Labor League.
    - [Independent Communist Labor League], Meetings and Personalities [6th National Convention, Communist Party Opposition], [1930s?] (Box 4, Item 222)
    - [Communist Party Opposition], Convention: Labor Day Weekend, Sep 1, 1935 (Box 4, Item 220)
    - [Communist Party Opposition], Washington's Birthday Weekend, Feb 1936 (Box 4, Item 219)
    - [Communist Party Opposition, 6th National Convention], 1936 (Box 1, Item 584)
    - [Independent Communist Labor League] 1937 National Convention of the ICLL or 1938 National Convention of the ICLL, or the 1938 New York District meeting of the ICLL., 1937, 1938 (Box 4, Item 12052)
    - [Independent Communist Labor League], 7th National Convention, New York City, ICLL Headquarters, 131 W. 33rd St.; District 65, Textile Workers, AFSCME 1717 [Signs include: "Hail Iberian Communist Youth," "P.O.U.M." (Workers Party of Marxist Unification) [Copy shot of document in German, Spanish and French, dated November 1939, translated: "Platform of International Workers Front Against War"], Jul 4, 1938 (Box 4, Item 641)
    - [Independent Communist Labor League] ICLL Meetings and Personalities, [1940s?] (Box 4, Item 223)
  - Subseries III:D: Liberal Party.
    - Liberal Party, undated (Box 4, Item 542)
- Series IV: Demonstrations.
  - [May Day Parade, 30-34th St. and 8th Ave.; "Bronx County Committee Communist Party"; [Signs: "Join the Communist Party Opposition USA"; "The CIO made Morgan Settle"; "Down with Imperialist War!"; "Free Mooney and Billings"; "Hail International Brigade"; "Support Anti-Lynching Bill"; "Workers School"; "Unity"; "Lincoln Battalion... Fighting in Spain."], [1930s?] (Box 1, Item 596)
  - [Parade at Union Square. 1937?][Signs: "The Union for All Office Workers Join the BS&AU" (Bookkeepers Stenographers, and Accountants Union); "Communist Party Opposition"; "Communist Party of New York State Workers of the World Unite!"], [1930s?] (Box 1, Item 594)
  - [Mass meeting in a stadium or large indoor auditorium; sign: "Federation German Workers Clubs of Greater New York--Hitler is Not Germany."], [1930s?] (Box 1, Item 590)
  - [Anti-William Randolph Hearst banner at a parade (perhaps May Day?): "Keep Hearst Out of Schools], [1930s?] (Box 1, Item 589)
  - [Speaker; banner: (Oppose the?) (Internati?)onal fascist offensive"], [1930s?] (Box 1, Item 588)
  - [Anti-Fascist convention; in background a banner/sign showing image of man wrenching swastika. Microphones show the speeches are being broadcast on radio station WEVD.], [1930s?] (Box 1, Item 587)
  - [Unlabeled. Street gathering? protest? demonstration?], [1930s?] (Box 4, Item 228)
  - Austrian Demonstration, 1934 (Box 1, Item 40)
  - May Day, 1934 (Box 1, Item 42)
  - May Day parade, 1935, New York City. (Box 4, Item 12051)
  - May Day, May 1, 1936 (Box 4, Item 85)
  - May Day, May 1, 1937 (Box 4, Item 86)
  - Ford Demonstration, Dec 24, 1937 (Box 4, Item 106)
  - May Day, May 1, 1938 (Box 4, Item 87)
  - Czech Demonstration, Columbus Circle/C.P.M., Mar 5, 1939 (Box 4, Item 600)
  - Charles Zimmerman [Two identical copy shots of an unidentified demonstration], [1940s?] (Box 2, Item 1003)
  - May Day, [1940s?] (Box 4, Item 696)
  - [Labor Demonstration, includes sign: "This is What We Demand for Xmas"], [1940s?] (Box 1, Item 585)
  - May Day, [1940s?] (Box 4, Item 98)
  - May Day, [1940?] (Box 4, Item 105)
  - May Day, [1940s?] (Box 4, Item 212)
  - San Francisco, Waterfront fight started when some members of the AFL Sailors Union of the Pacific Coast fought their way through a picket line established by the CIO Ship Scalers and Painters Union., Oct 15, 1940 (Box not specified, Item 549)
  - [Dressmakers Demonstration], [1950s?] (Box 4, Item 691)
  - [Local 1-S DSWU--RWDSU May's Protest], [1950s?] (Box 4, Item 698)
  - Civil Rights Rally [Madison Square Garden] Celeb., May 24, 1956 (Box 4, Item 690)
  - Labor Day, Sep 1, 1959 (Box 1, Item 721)
  - Labor Day, Sep 1, 1959 (Box 4, Item 693)
  - Pickets: South African Embassy [Anti-Apartheid Protest], Mar 30, 1960 (Box 4, Item 697)
  - Labor Day, Sep 5, 1960 (Box 4, Item 694)
  - Labor Day, S.I.U., Sep 5, 1960 (Box 1, Item 722)
  - Kennedy Rally: Garment District, Oct 27, 1960 (Box 4, Item 692)
  - District 65 Kennedy Rally: Garment District, Oct 27, 1960 (Box 2, Item 934)
  - [Labor Day], Sep 1, 1961 (Box 4, Item 695)
  - Labor Day, Sep 1, 1961 (Box 1, Item 723)
- Series V: Strikes.
  - [Copy shot] Trolley Strike, 1886 (Box 2, Item 936)
  - [Copy shots of:] Labor/Seaman's Strike? England/Lining up for Strike Benefits, [1930s?] (Box 1, Item 553)
  - [Copy shots of:] Strike: 11/24/36 "We are prepared to fight to the finish"; "Protesting imprisonment of 7 seamen convicted of possessing dynamite during tanker strike 20 months earlier. Building is San Francisco Standard Oil"; 11/18/36 Strike bound S.S. Washington sails. Picketing US lines; Picketing Matson Piers, San Francisco 11/5/36; San Francisco "Three a Day" 12/7/36; Began May 9, 1936 (Box 1, Item 497)
  - Strikes: International Seafarers Union Members on Strike, 1936 (Box 1, Item 66)
  - [Copy shots of:] Strike: Houston, Texas; Wilbur Dickey Dumped, Dickey Patrolman M.F.O.W., 1936 (Box 1, Item 50)
  - Strike: Meeting in Lyceum Hall, 1936 (Box 1, Item 49)
  - [Copy shots of:] Union Square mass meeting of waterfront workers 12/12/36 Strike began October 29, 1936 (Box 1, Item 48)
  - Registering for Picket Duty, 1936 (Box 1, Item 41)
  - Lang News Strike, [1940s?] (Box 4, Item 601)
  - Met News Strike, [1940s?] (Box 4, Item 215)
  - Cohn Hall Marx Strike, [1940s?] (Box 4, Item 213)
  - Strike?: Roosevelt Home Hyde Park, NY, [1950s?] (Box 2, Item 938)
- Series VI: Miscellaneous Events.
  - [Unlabeled Convention], [1930s?] (Box 1, Item 593)
  - [An unidentified man (almost certainly New York City Mayor Fiorello LaGuardia) speaking at a podium at mass meeting or convention, his speech being broadcast on radio stations WEVD and WMCA; also, General Hugh Johnson], [1930s?] (Box 1, Item 591)
  - Welcome to Soviet North Pole [Air] Flyers [Sign: "Soviet Pioneers of the Air"], [1930s?] (Box 4, Item 702)
  - Banquet for Bob Edwards, Jun 23, 1938 (Box 4, Item 216)
  - Gen. Eisenhower Museum of Art, Apr 1, 1946 (Box 4, Item 644)
  - Hyde Park ,Roosevelt, Sep 7, 1946 (Box 1, Item 498)
  - Delegation to Hyde Park -- Eleanor Roosevelt, [1950s?] (Box 1, Item 724)
  - Cora Bacor, Winner of UN Essay Contest Mayor Wagner, Eleanor Roosevelt, Oct 24, 1957 (Box 2, Item 928)
  - News Alliance Capitol Funeral, May 6, 1958 (Box 4, Item 701)
  - Haym Salomon Home Annual Meeting, 1970 (Box 6, Item 12053)
  - Unidentified speaker addressing a crowd of spectators at an outdoor meeting, undated (Box 6, Item 12054, Item 12055, Item 12056)
  - Miscellaneous Events (Box 8)
- Series VII: Personalities.
  - Alsop[?], J. H.S., [Oct 1946?] (Box 1, Item 556)
  - Murray Baron [?], Dec 9, 1958 (Box 2, Item 951)
  - Gus Beam; R. Elber[?], [1950s?] (Box 2, Item 952)
  - Max Bloom, Oct 18, 1950 (Box 2, Item 953)
  - Mel Bloom, May 15, 1956 (Box 2, Item 954)
  - Boklaw [?] Family, Aug 5, 1951 (Box 2, Item 955)
  - Burton [Burtan?] Family, Sep 19, 1953 (Box 1, Item 726)
  - Val Burtan, Sep 24, 1958 (Box 2, Item 956)
  - Burtan, V.G. [Val Burtan?], Oct 1, 1961 (Box 2, Item 957)
  - CIO James Carey, Jun 1, 1950 (Box 2, Item 958)
  - David L. Cole [Director of Federal Mediation and Conciliation Service], [1950s?] (Box 2, Item 959)
  - Lara Colombia T.U. Head [Meeting (luncheon?) in a small conference room], 1950 (Box 2, Item 1004)
  - Ely Culbertson [speaking at a dinner], 1946 (Box 1, Item 47)
  - Lester Davis, [1960s?] (Box 1, Item 727)
  - Linda DeDefler [sp?], May 1, 1960 (Box 2, Item 960)
  - Dwight D. Eisenhower, [1940s?] (Box 4, Item 704)
  - Eisenstadt, [1950s?] (Box 2, Item 964)
  - James Farrell, [1950s?] (Box 2, Item 966)
  - Flynn [Board of Education?], [1950s?] (Box 2, Item 961)
  - Carl J. Friedman of Howard University, 1946 (Box 1, Item 45)
  - Arthur Goldberg (Speaks -- Jewish Labor Committee), Jun 18, 1959 (Box 2, Item 967)
  - Gene Goldsmith, Oct 1, 1956 (Box 2, Item 963)
  - Paul Hall, Sep 23, 1953 (Box 4, Item 703)
  - [Copy shots of] George Harrison, President, Railway and Steamship Clerks, AFL, [1950s?] (Box 2, Item 965)
  - Morris Iushewitz, Aug 1, 1950 (Box 2, Item 971)
  - WLIB [Radio], Arnold J. Jaffe, Mar 14, 1951 (Box 1, Item 652)
  - G. [George?] Jessel, [1950s?] (Box 4, Item 705)
  - Arthur Kalster, Carnegie Hall Meeting, 1948 (Box 1, Item 46)
  - Dr. Karl [?], [1940s?] (Box 4, Item 226)
  - Murray Koening, Nov 27, 1951 (Box 2, Item 968)
  - Political; La Guardia; Thomas Dewey; Alex [Rose]; Dewey and Luigi Antonini, [1930s?] (Box 3, Item 1670)
  - Mort Lawrence, Gawdy 26 Bway, Oct 22, 1959 (Box 2, Item 970)
  - John L. Lewis; Anti-Nazi Meeting; Madison Square Garden; Note DD Johnson [David Dubinsky in corner], [1930s?] (Box 3, Item 1674)
  - Jay Lovestone, 1934 (Box 1, Item 62)
  - [Jay Lovestone], [1940s?] (Box 4, Item 227)
  - [Jay Lovestone], [1940s?] (Box 4, Item 603)
  - J. J. [Jules?] Manson Portrait, Nov 23, 1956 (Box 2, Item 974)
  - J. J. [Jules?] Manson Portrai, Feb 17, 1957 (Box 2, Item 975)
  - Mr. Midgen Portrait, 1948 (Box 1, Item 44)
  - R. Mieblum [? Nieblux?], [1950s?] (Box 2, Item 1008)
  - [Copy shots] Minkoff [?] -- Parents, [1950s?] (Box 2, Item 1005)
  - Tom Mooney; New[bold?] Morris and T. M.; Antononi and T. M.; Welcome in [Madison Square Garden], [1930s?] (Box 3, Item 1673)
  - John Mozen [Urzan?], [1950s?] (Box 2, Item 1007)
  - Saby Nehama, Nov 9, 1950 (Box 2, Item 1006)
  - [A man (Oscar Newman?) accompanying a delegation of women and one child on a visit to Franklin D. Roosevelt's home, Hyde Park.], Sep 26, 1946 (Box 1, Item 65)
  - O'Donnel and Schwartz Accident, May 21, 1951 (Box 2, Item 1009)
  - Mayor William O'Dwyer, [Jun 1946) (Box 4, Item 544)
  - Harvey Olnick, Jun 1, 1949 (Box 1, Item 75)
  - Harvey Olnick Passport, [1950s?] (Box 2, Item 1010)
  - Harvey Olnick, Feb 19, 1954 (Box 1, Item 728)
  - Alex W. -- L. Persands [?] [Exterior, man posed with two women], [1920s?] (Box 1, Item 735)
  - Rose Pesotta Family, Sep 10, 1960 (Box 1, Item 729)
  - Bob Richardson, Jan 6, 1960 (Box 2, Item 1012)
  - Bob Richardson, Mar 17, 1960 (Box 2, Item 979)
  - Richard Riebo [?], [1950s?] (Box 2, Item 1011)
  - Rogan, Larry, Textile [Textile Workers?] C.I.[O?], [1950s?] (Box 2, Item 980)
  - Eleanor Roosevelt, [1940s?] (Box 4, Item 543)
  - Franklin D. Roosevelt, Portrait, undated (Box 6, Item 12057)
  - Samovodin [Samorodin?], Milton; Swearing in by [Judge] Matt Levy, Dec 29, 1951 (Box 2, Item 1001)
  - I. Scharfman at L.A.S. Affair[?], Jan 31, 1951 (Box 2, Item 981)
  - Schukin, Dave, [1960s?] (Box 2, Item 982)
  - Seabury, [1950s?] (Box 2, Item 983)
  - Bernard Seaman [Portaits], May 1, 1949 (Box 1, Item 74)
  - Seaman [Bernard Seaman's Daughter], [1950s?] (Box 2, Item 987)
  - [Bernard Seaman with family], [1950s?] (Box 2, Item 986)
  - [Bernard Seaman -- labor cartoonist -- Friend of Daniel Nilva's], [1950s?] (Box 2, Item 984)
  - [Bernard] Seaman, [1950s?] (Box 1, Item 730)
  - [Bernard Seaman Family], [1950s?] (Box 1, Item 732)
  - [Bernard Seaman and Family], [1950s?] (Box 1, Item 733)
  - [Bernard] Seaman, [Croton?] Meeting, Nov 25, 1950 (Box 1, Item 837)
  - Bernard Seaman, Feb 19, 1954 (Box 2, Item 985)
  - B. [Bernard] Seaman, Oct 1, 1954 (Box 1, Item 731)
  - [Copy shots] Dr. Ralph Sepsin, [1950s?] (Box 2, Item 988)
  - Horatio [?] Seymour; Tammany Club; 364 W 23 St., Jan 31, 1952 (Box 2, Item 989)
  - Frances Smith, Jan 24, 1957 (Box 2, Item 990)
  - Dr. C. Snyder, Sep 12, 1957 (Box 2, Item 991)
  - Enrich [?] Springer. [Springer appears to be an African-American office-holder.] Judge Matt Levy Swearing in [? on Bible?], Oct 24, 1955 (Box 2, Item 972)
  - AFL-CIO Max Steinbock [Steinbach?], [1950s?] (Box 2, Item 993)
  - Julie Steinberg, Dec 1, 1949 (Box 1, Item 64)
  - Lydia Tolstoy, Mar 20, 1951 (Box 2, Item 978)
  - Trare [sp?] Leimpkin, 1934 (Box 1, Item 77)
  - [New York City Mayor Wagner presents Miss Union Maid with a bouquet.], [1950s?] (Box 2, Item 949)
  - Arthur K. Watson. VP -- IBM World Trade Corp, [1950s?] (Box 2, Item 995)
  - E. Welsh [Labor], 1934 (Box 1, Item 63)
  - Edward K Welsh, 82 W. Montcalm, Detroit, Mich., Jan 11, 1957 (Box 2, Item 997)
  - Morton Wishengrad at typewriter, Jul 19, 1950 (Box 2, Item 996)
  - [Bertram D.] Wolfe, [1950s?] (Box 2, Item 998)
  - [Bertram] D. Wolfe, 1934 (Box 1, Item 76)
  - Matthew Woll, [1950s?] (Box 2, Item 1000)
  - [Matthew] Woll and Eric Jonston, [1950s?] (Box 2, Item 999)
  - Lou Yagoda, Nov 24, 1959 (Box 1, Item 734)
  - Zimmerman, Charles, [1950s?] (Box 2, Item 1002)
- Series VIII: Other Clients.
  - Subseries VIII:A: American Veterans Committee.
    - [American Veterans Committee]; Dinner Gross, Tyler and Goldsmith, Michael Straight; Belmont Plaza, Oct 12, 1956 (Box 2, Item 1013)
    - Eleanor Roosevelt; NY [American Veterans Committee. 14th National Convention.], May 1961 (Box 2, Item 1014)
    - Eleanor Roosevelt. Convention [American Veterans Committee] [Commodore Hotel], May 1961 (Box 4, Item 689)
    - [American Veterans Committee]; Award to Adlai Stevenson at US Mission to UN, Apr 20, 1962 (Box 2, Item 1015)
  - Subseries VIII:B: Jewish Consumptive Relief Association.
    - City of Hope; Tuvim Dinner; Richard Wright [Assistant Secretary of State], Apr 21, 1951 (Box 2, Item 1016)
    - City of Hope; Torch of Hope Award to M. Tobin Waldorf Astoria, May 9, 1951 (Box 2, Item 1017)
    - City of Hope [Jewish Consumptive Relief Association] Luncheon CIO NY Director, Sep 21, 1951 (Box 2, Item 1019)
    - City of Hope [Jewish Consumptive Relief Association], Feb 10, 1952 (Box 2, Item 1020)
    - Deborah Sanitorium Luncheon; Waldorf-Astoria; [Jewish Consumptive Relief Association] [Damaged negatives separated], Jun 17, 1954 (Box 3, Item 1862)
    - Deborah Sanitorium [Jewish Consumptive Relief Association] Patient [from?] -- Holland. Idlewild [Airport?], Aug 14, 1954 (Box 3, Item 1036)
    - Deborah Hospital; Knitgoods Industry; [Separated as Damaged]; [Jewish Consumptive Relief Association], Dec 26, 1954 (Box 3, Item 1864)
    - City of Hope Luncheon [Jewish Consumptive Relief Association] Hotel Pierre Roof. George Jessel [speaker?] and [Jennie] Grossinger, Jun 16, 1955 (Box 2, Item 1021)
    - Deborah Sanitorium [Jewish Consumptive Relief Association]. Mrs. Henry [?] Epstein wife of Deputy Mayor, Sep 14, 1955 (Box 2, Item 1022)
    - Deborah Sanitorium [Jewish Consumptive Relief Association]. Hotel Astor 8th Floor Ballroom; Honoring Ben[?] Paul; Belt Industry Fabulous Belts; Henry Schwartz, Local 40, Nathan Mintz, Ben Mintz, DC, Oct 27, 1955 (Box 2, Item 1023)
    - Deborah Sanitorium [Jewish Consumptive Relief Association] Plaza Hotel Mr. and Mrs. Epstein, Nov 15, 1955 (Box 2, Item 1024)
    - Deborah Sanitorium [Jewish Consumptive Relief Association], Bill Schnitzler Dinner Commodore, Nov 22, 1955 (Box 2, Item 1025)
    - Deborah Sanitorium [Jewish Consumptive Relief Association] Portrait of unidentified man], Oct 4, 1956 (Box 2, Item 1026)
    - Deborah Sanitorium [Jewish Consumptive Relief Association] [Award to J. Irwin Shapiro.] Waldorf-Astoria, Nov 14, 1956 (Box 2, Item 1027)
    - Deborah Sanitorium [Jewish Consumptive Relief Association] [Award to] Walter Reuther; Commodore Hotel, May 10, 1957 (Box 2, Item 1028)
    - Deborah Sanitorium [Jewish Consumptive Relief Association]; Belt Industry, Commodore; Herb Novick, Oct 24, 1957 (Box 2, Item 1029)
    - Deborah Sanitorium [Jewish Consumptive Relief Association] [Banquet at] Waldorf-Astoria, Dec 22, 1957 (Box 2, Item 1030)
    - Deborah Sanitorium [Jewish Consumptive Relief Association]; Copy Neg Aerial View Hospital, Feb 17, 1958 (Box 2, Item 1031)
    - Deborah Sanitorium [Jewish Consumpitve Relief Association] Groups [Group shots of women presenting a "Heart of Gold" certificate to another woman.], Mar 13, 1958 (Box 2, Item 1032)
    - Deborah Sanitorium [Jewish Consumptive Relief Association] Exec. Comm. Hotel Astor, Apr 27, 1958 (Box 3, Item 1033)
    - Deborah Sanitorium. [Jewish Consumptive Relief Association]. Starks[?] Office [Group of people displaying a New York City mayor's proclamation; group includes shots of a little boy and a performer with a ventriloquist's dummy.], Apr 28, 1958 (Box 3, Item 1034)
    - Deborah Sanitorium [Jewish Consumptive Relief Association] Women's Comm. Hqtrs, Jun 2, 1958 (Box 3, Item 1037)
    - Deborah Sanitorium [Jewish Consumptive Relief Association] Mayor's Office, Paul Winchell, Jun 18, 1958 (Box 3, Item 1035)
    - Deborah Sanitorium [Jewish Consumptive Relief Association] Meeting; Waldorf, Oct 2, 1958 (Box 3, Item 1056)